# YESHESVI KADIYALA

# USER EXPERIENCE RESEARCHER AND DEVELOPER

7348810801 yesh@umich.edu

I am a detail-oriented professional, who really takes up all opportunities to learn and get better. I have worked as a customer oriented agent at the University of Michigan Health System's IT Company for over a year now. I have worked with multiple CRM solutions like Zendesk, Salesforce and also over the phone. Furthermore, I have experience interviewing clients for requirements to design a product and gathering data from users to evaluate a product in their shoes.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Health system, USA Jan 2014 – Jan 2015

# University of Michigan TECH SUPPORT - COMPUTER CONSULTANT II

I've worked at the Medical School Information Services (MSIS) at the University of Michigan Health System as an IT professional who is customer faced. My primary job at MSIS was to handle the phone calls, manage tickets on Zendesk and go on-site and help the clients.

#### Jackson Police Department, USA Dec 2014 - April 2015

#### USER EXPERIENCE RESEARCHER

In a combined venture by the city of Jackson and University of Michigan, I was part of a team that designed and developed an Anonymous texting platform for the public of Jackson to send in tips to the police. The focus of the project was minimal cost, minimal infrastructure and viability for the public.

#### Working Bikes May 2014 - June 2014

#### TECHNOLOGY CONSULTANT - VOLUNTEER

I've helped a non-profit organization, Working Bikes to develop a technological blueprint in order to help them finance their technology needs in a prioritized and efficient way. I have conducted interviews with the staff, management, donors and customers to figure out the process of the company and find out areas in which technology can make a difference.

#### COIGN Tech April 2012 - July 2012

#### Android Developer Intern

I've designed and developed a couple of android apps. One is a security app to display user's information on the lock screen (this feature was implemented after Android 4.0 natively). The other app I've developed is a universal file directory that can show any file type selected (movies, pictures, music etc.).

#### **EDUCATION**

# University of Michigan, USA 2013 – present

# Master of Science in Information

I am pursuing a Master's degree in Human Computer Interaction at the School of Information. A major part of the program is to enhance technological accessibility to users. In the program, we have learned to understand and decipher user needs and use the same to design a workflow around the user.

# Jawaharlal Technological University, Hyderabad 2009 - 2013

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science

### **SKILLS**

#### User Experience,

-User / Client Research and Evaluation - Front end design with bootstrap

- Rapid Prototyping - Digital Prototyping

- Wireframing - Data Synthesis and Mining

#### Programming,

- HTML5, CSS3, JSON -Python 2.7 & 3

- Object Oriented Programming, Java -JavaScript

-Android Applications, design and development